

UX/UI Designer

Naomioalao@gmail.com

www.Naomialaodesign

Education

UI Design Program
CareerFoundry
2021-2022

University of Sheffield Journalism Studies 2015-2019

Skills

User Research Visual Design

Branding Wireframing

Usability testing User Flows

Prototyping Frontend

Typography Style Guide

Responsive

Design

HTML

JavaScript

CSS

Frontend

Key Strengths

Leadership Delegation

Communication Innovative

Research Critical

Thinking

Problem-Solving

Time

Inquisitive Management

Interests

Travelling Music

Psychology Reading

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Behance (2

About me

A UX/UI designer passion about building user-centric experiences on functional, clean, and accessible interfaces. An inquisitive problem solver experienced in gathering quantitative and qualitative data to create intuitive designs.

UX/UI Experience

Travel Buddy - Web responsive app

Jul 2021 - Jan 2022 | CareerFoundry

Taking a mobile first approach I developed a travel app using breakpoints, grid systems, and design patterns, for various screen sizes. I conducted user interviews and implemented ideas from the data to create user personas, wireframe, and prototypes. Following a style guide I made informed design decisions with user testing results.

Global Citizen - Web responsive app

Apr 2022 - May 2022 | CareerFoundry

Following Apple's Human Interactive Guidelines and Google's Material Design, I created a language app for iOS and android. I conducted a competitor analysis, created wireframes, user flows, a style guide end- to-end prototypes. This two-pronged approach helped me develop a keen awareness of the nuances in design systems, typefaces, functionality of both operating systems.

Target - Web responsive app

May 2022 - Jul 2022 | CareerFoundry

Target, another web responsive money saving tool, focused on helping users actualize their monetary goals. A process I learnt in this project was developing brand guidelines to set the parameters of what was in alignment to a brand. This included consolidating Imagery, guiding principles, logo, colours, writing style and typography into a document.

Work experience

Graduate Technical Operator

Jun 2019 - Oct 2019

My role was centred around localising cinematographic content for esteemed movie studios (Disney, 20th Century Fox, Warner Bros, Paramount, Imax, Dogwoof, Eone). On any given day I edited video material, encoded, and transcoded files into a variety of formats, localised content, and edited creative cutdowns.

Assisting editor and videographer

Dec 2019 - Sep 2021

I worked as an editor and videographer for Marv Brown films, an independent wedding and music video production company. My duties include filing and organizing source footage, assisting on-location shoots, setting lighting and audio equipment, capturing behind the scenes, and operating industry-level equipment like gimbals, and stabilisers.